[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "What has it been like to be you in the last year?", "question_tokens": ["What", "has", "it", "been", "like", "to", "be", "you", "in", "the", "last", "year", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "CHWARZENEGGER: Well, you know, I always have been very successful in my professional life.", "answer_tokens": ["CHWARZENEGGER", ":", "Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "always", "have", "been", "very", "successful", "in", "my", "professional", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WP", "TO", "VB", "CC", "WP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "Have you felt -- have you felt it's been too much or not?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "felt", "--", "have", "you", "felt", "it", "'s", "been", "too", "much", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "You know, I never tell the press what to write and what to say.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "never", "tell", "the", "press", "what", "to", "write", "and", "what", "to", "say", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 82, "question": "And you're probably not reading half of it, right, I would imagine?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "'re", "probably", "not", "reading", "half", "of", "it", ",", "right", ",", "I", "would", "imagine", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 83, "answer": "I would say I don't read any of it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "say", "I", "do", "n't", "read", "any", "of", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", ",", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", ",", "CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "And who's been -- who's been the rocks, if you like, for you in this?", "question_tokens": ["And", "who", "'s", "been", "--", "who", "'s", "been", "the", "rocks", ",", "if", "you", "like", ",", "for", "you", "in", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "I think that there's a tremendous amount of people that have shown great support, and then there's a lot of people that have let me know that they're disappointed and it's perfectly fine, including my children that were disappointed in that action and inevitably my wife was very disappointed, and so, it's -- look, it's my -- it's my fault.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "there", "'s", "a", "tremendous", "amount", "of", "people", "that", "have", "shown", "great", "support", ",", "and", "then", "there", "'s", "a", "lot", "of", "people", "that", "have", "let", "me", "know", "that", "they", "'re", "disappointed", "and", "it", "'s", "perfectly", "fine", ",", "including", "my", "children", "that", "were", "disappointed", "in", "that", "action", "and", "inevitably", "my", "wife", "was", "very", "disappointed", ",", "and", "so", ",", "it", "'s", "--", "look", ",", "it", "'s", "my", "--", "it", "'s", "my", "fault", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Maria"]}, "docId": "121002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 103, "question": "Do you think there is a good chance you can get back together?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "there", "is", "a", "good", "chance", "you", "can", "get", "back", "together", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 104, "answer": "I cannot speak for Maria.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "can", "not", "speak", "for", "Maria", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "Was it more that?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "more", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "I would say that it makes no difference.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "say", "that", "it", "makes", "no", "difference", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "IN", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "What was the reality of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "reality", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "I think the book goes into the details of the whole thing and I think that people, when they read it, they will get an understanding of what the whole thing was about, and that I leave it at that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "book", "goes", "into", "the", "details", "of", "the", "whole", "thing", "and", "I", "think", "that", "people", ",", "when", "they", "read", "it", ",", "they", "will", "get", "an", "understanding", "of", "what", "the", "whole", "thing", "was", "about", ",", "and", "that", "I", "leave", "it", "at", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 161, "question": "Could I see her, please?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "I", "see", "her", ",", "please", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "Where is she?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "is", "she", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "Look, it may take awhile.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "it", "may", "take", "awhile", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "Or is that now like the bodybuilding, done?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "is", "that", "now", "like", "the", "bodybuilding", ",", "done", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "CHWARZENEGGER: Well, you know, I have really no interest to go and run for office or anything like that.", "answer_tokens": ["CHWARZENEGGER", ":", "Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "have", "really", "no", "interest", "to", "go", "and", "run", "for", "office", "or", "anything", "like", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "Was it harder than you thought, being governor?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "harder", "than", "you", "thought", ",", "being", "governor", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "Well, first of all, let me just tell you that I didn't care what it takes in order to fix the state.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "let", "me", "just", "tell", "you", "that", "I", "did", "n't", "care", "what", "it", "takes", "in", "order", "to", "fix", "the", "state", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NNS", ",", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "What's your advice?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "advice", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "I think that, you know, with debates, the most important thing is to be real.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", ",", "you", "know", ",", "with", "debates", ",", "the", "most", "important", "thing", "is", "to", "be", "real", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John F. Kennedy"]}, "docId": "121002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 208, "question": "Are you surprised that in America, the country that gave you the opportunity to become what you are, that they would now turn on somebody for being what used to be the great American dream?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "surprised", "that", "in", "America", ",", "the", "country", "that", "gave", "you", "the", "opportunity", "to", "become", "what", "you", "are", ",", "that", "they", "would", "now", "turn", "on", "somebody", "for", "being", "what", "used", "to", "be", "the", "great", "American", "dream", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 209, "answer": "Well, first of all, as you know, John F. Kennedy came from a very rich family.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "as", "you", "know", ",", "John", "F.", "Kennedy", "came", "from", "a", "very", "rich", "family", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "I know you haven't decided who you're going to vote for in all this time, but right now, if you had to vote tomorrow, who would you vote for?", "question_tokens": ["I", "know", "you", "have", "n't", "decided", "who", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "vote", "for", "in", "all", "this", "time", ",", "but", "right", "now", ",", "if", "you", "had", "to", "vote", "tomorrow", ",", "who", "would", "you", "vote", "for", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "I would have to first listen to the debates.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "have", "to", "first", "listen", "to", "the", "debates", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "So they're that important to you?", "question_tokens": ["So", "they", "'re", "that", "important", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "It's very important.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "very", "important", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NNS", "DT", "RB", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 239, "question": "I mean how -- what do you think?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "how", "--", "what", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 240, "answer": "We maybe would have done things a little differently, but I can guarantee you that the president is doing everything that he can to solve the problems.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "maybe", "would", "have", "done", "things", "a", "little", "differently", ",", "but", "I", "can", "guarantee", "you", "that", "the", "president", "is", "doing", "everything", "that", "he", "can", "to", "solve", "the", "problems", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "When you go back to that little boy, Arnold Schwarzenegger, what was it about you, do you think, that gave you the drive to achieve all this?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "go", "back", "to", "that", "little", "boy", ",", "Arnold", "Schwarzenegger", ",", "what", "was", "it", "about", "you", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "that", "gave", "you", "the", "drive", "to", "achieve", "all", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "I think that I had the most extraordinary talent in visualizing.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "I", "had", "the", "most", "extraordinary", "talent", "in", "visualizing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Arnold Schwarzenegger"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "Can you still do the 400 pound stuff?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "still", "do", "the", "400", "pound", "stuff", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "I cannot do the 400 pound stuff anymore.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "can", "not", "do", "the", "400", "pound", "stuff", "anymore", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "What's the most you lift these days?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "most", "you", "lift", "these", "days", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "I lift every day.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "lift", "every", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "Your idea of light weight and mine are probably two different things, aren't they?", "question_tokens": ["Your", "idea", "of", "light", "weight", "and", "mine", "are", "probably", "two", "different", "things", ",", "are", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "VBP", "RB", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "Maybe is a different thing, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Maybe", "is", "a", "different", "thing", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "CD", ",", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "What is your idea of a light weight these days?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "idea", "of", "a", "light", "weight", "these", "days", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "I still am lifting with 150, 200 pounds.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "still", "am", "lifting", "with", "150", ",", "200", "pounds", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "VBD", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 294, "question": "How many sit ups?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "sit", "ups", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 295, "answer": "Five hundred sit ups and leg raises.", "answer_tokens": ["Five", "hundred", "sit", "ups", "and", "leg", "raises", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "Wait a minute, 500 sit ups, really?", "question_tokens": ["Wait", "a", "minute", ",", "500", "sit", "ups", ",", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CD", "NN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "I ride the bicycle every day for an hour.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "ride", "the", "bicycle", "every", "day", "for", "an", "hour", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 304, "question": "If you all got in a room together and had a fight, the Expendables, who would win?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "all", "got", "in", "a", "room", "together", "and", "had", "a", "fight", ",", "the", "Expendables", ",", "who", "would", "win", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "DT", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "CHWARZENEGGER: Whatever the director says.", "answer_tokens": ["CHWARZENEGGER", ":", "Whatever", "the", "director", "says", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "Was it something that you felt by the time you closed the last chapter and finished and read it through, you were glad you had done it, even though you may get criticized from certain quarters?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "something", "that", "you", "felt", "by", "the", "time", "you", "closed", "the", "last", "chapter", "and", "finished", "and", "read", "it", "through", ",", "you", "were", "glad", "you", "had", "done", "it", ",", "even", "though", "you", "may", "get", "criticized", "from", "certain", "quarters", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "I think that it was a great idea to do the book.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "it", "was", "a", "great", "idea", "to", "do", "the", "book", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "If Maria's watching this, and she might well be watching this, what would you say to her?", "question_tokens": ["If", "Maria", "'s", "watching", "this", ",", "and", "she", "might", "well", "be", "watching", "this", ",", "what", "would", "you", "say", "to", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "POS", "VBG", "DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "DT", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "I would just say sorry for what I've done.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "just", "say", "sorry", "for", "what", "I", "'ve", "done", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Maria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "You think -- do you deserve to be forgiven, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["You", "think", "--", "do", "you", "deserve", "to", "be", "forgiven", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "I think everyone deserves to be forgiven and get a break.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "everyone", "deserves", "to", "be", "forgiven", "and", "get", "a", "break", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "Most Catholics are in recovery, aren't they?", "question_tokens": ["Most", "Catholics", "are", "in", "recovery", ",", "are", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJS", "NNP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "That's why I wrote the book.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "why", "I", "wrote", "the", "book", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "So how long did the Nun thing really last in reality?", "question_tokens": ["So", "how", "long", "did", "the", "Nun", "thing", "really", "last", "in", "reality", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "It lasted about three or four years.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "lasted", "about", "three", "or", "four", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", ":", "JJ", "NN"], "qSentId": 430, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "I did mass in my house, literally, (inaudible)", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "mass", "in", "my", "house", ",", "literally", ",", "(", "inaudible", ")"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "How you going to feel if your book, \"Bad Habits, Confessions,\" being next to Arnold Schwarzenegger's book on the book stands?", "question_tokens": ["How", "you", "going", "to", "feel", "if", "your", "book", ",", "``", "Bad", "Habits", ",", "Confessions", ",", "''", "being", "next", "to", "Arnold", "Schwarzenegger", "'s", "book", "on", "the", "book", "stands", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "``", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "''", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "What a perfect pair, I would think.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "a", "perfect", "pair", ",", "I", "would", "think", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Arnold Schwarzenegger"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "Impregnated their housekeepers?", "question_tokens": ["Impregnated", "their", "housekeepers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "Close.", "answer_tokens": ["Close", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ":", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "Do you have any view of the election, talking of bad habits?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "any", "view", "of", "the", "election", ",", "talking", "of", "bad", "habits", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "CCARTHY: No, I don't, only because I've learned in my own -- how do I put it -- risky words I've used in my career to question people and make statements, it's -- I can't even go into politics.", "answer_tokens": ["CCARTHY", ":", "No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", ",", "only", "because", "I", "'ve", "learned", "in", "my", "own", "--", "how", "do", "I", "put", "it", "--", "risky", "words", "I", "'ve", "used", "in", "my", "career", "to", "question", "people", "and", "make", "statements", ",", "it", "'s", "--", "I", "ca", "n't", "even", "go", "into", "politics", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "For any men watching, you are single, right?", "question_tokens": ["For", "any", "men", "watching", ",", "you", "are", "single", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "I am so single.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "so", "single", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "Are you on the hunt?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "on", "the", "hunt", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "No, no, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "Little beady eye?", "question_tokens": ["Little", "beady", "eye", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "That's right.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 501, "question": "You brought him up pretty much on your own, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "brought", "him", "up", "pretty", "much", "on", "your", "own", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 502, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121002pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "Oh, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]